When I travel all around the world to
make this show, and I'm writing scripts,
like in our latest episode about
diamonds, there were these really cool
released CIA documents about who grew
the first diamonds. I really don't want
anyone looking over my shoulder, which
is why I'm using this for privacy. Most
companies do this with a plastic filter
that you stick on. It's like polarized
sunglasses for your [music] laptop. They
work, but they cut your brightness in
half and I lose them constantly. But in
this device, there's another layer
hidden inside the display. Thinner than
three human hairs. [music] So when I
click this, extra voltage causes
molecules in that layer to tilt, so that
light going straight forward toward you
passes through clean, but light going
sideways, like to those nosey people
over there, gets distorted. It's super
easy to turn off and on. I spend a lot
of time now traveling for this show, and
it makes a big difference to have
privacy features on a commercial device
that work the way that I work. If you
want to check it out, go to this link
right here.